Kael mss., 1939-2001 LMC 3004
Lilly Library
- II. Directors
  - Russell, Ken (Box 67)
    - Women in Love., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 67)
    - Materials concerning other films and Russell, (2 folders) (see also: Box 116) (Box 67)
  - Rydell, Mark (Box 67)
    - Cinderella Liberty., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 67)
    - On Golden Pond., (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - The River., (2 folders) (Box 67)
    - The Rose., notes, clippings (Box 67)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 67)
  - Sagan, Leontine (Box 67)
    - Mädchen in Uniform., photographs, clippings (Box 67)
  - Saks, Gene (Box 67)
    - Brighton Beach Memoirs., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 67)
  - Santell, Alfred (Box 67)
    - Winterset., (see also: Box 116) (Box 67)
  - Saura, Carlos (Box 67)
    - ¡Ay, Carmela!, notes, publicity, clippings (Box 67)
  - Sautet, Claude (Box 67)
    - Mado., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 67)
    - Quelques jours avec moi (A Few Days with Me)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 67)
    - Vincent, François, Paul...et les autres (Vincent, François, Paul and the Others)., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 67)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 67)
  - Saville, Victor (Box 67)
    - South Riding., photographs, clippings (Box 67)
  - Savini, Tom (Box 67)
    - Night of the Living Dead., press kit, clippings (Box 67)
  - Sayles, John (Box 67)
    - Baby It's You., clippings (Box 67)
    - The Brother from Another Planet., press release, clippings (Box 67)
    - Lianna., notes, clippings (Box 67)
    - Matewan., clippings (Box 67)
    - Return of the Secaucus 7., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 67)
    - Materials concerning other films and Sayles (Box 67)
  - Scanlan, Joseph L. (Box 67)
    - The World's Oldest Living Bridesmaid (television)., script (Box 67)
  - Schaefer, George (Box 67)
    - F. Scott Fitzgerald and "The Last of the Belles" (television)., notes, clippings (Box 67)
  - Schaffner, Franklin J. (Box 67)
    - The Boys from Brazil., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 67)
    - Islands in the Stream., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 67)
    - Nicholas and Alexandra., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 67)
    - Papillon., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 67)
    - Planet of the Apes., publicity, clippings (Box 67)
    - Sphinx., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 67)
    - Yes, Giorgio., notes, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 67)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 67)
  - Schamoni, Peter (Box 68)
    - Frühlingssinfonie (Spring Symphony - U.S.)., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 68)
  - Schary, Dore (Box 68)
    - Act One., notes (Box 68)
  - Schatzberg, Jerry (Box 68)
    - Honeysuckle Rose., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 68)
    - No Small Affair., notes, clippings (Box 68)
    - The Panic in Needle Park., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - Puzzle of a Downfall Child., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - The Seduction of Joe Tynan., (for publicity see: Box 116) (Box 68)
    - Street Smart., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 68)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 68)
  - Scheerer, Robert (Box 68)
    - How to Beat the High Co$t of Living., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
  - Schepisi, Fred (Box 68)
    - Barbarosa., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 68)
    - The Chant of Jimmie Blacksmith., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - A Cry in the Dark., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 68)
    - The Devil's Playground., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - Iceman., (4 folders) (Box 68)
    - Plenty., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 68)
    - Roxanne., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - The Russia House., notes, publicity, photographs, color slides, clippings (Box 68)
    - Six Degrees of Separation., (3 folders) (Box 68)
  - Schertzinger, Victor (Box 68)
    - The Mikado., photographs, clippings (Box 68)
  - Schibli, Paul (Box 68)
    - The Nutcracker Prince., photographs (Box 68)
  - Schlesinger, John (Box 68)
    - The Believers., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 68)
    - Darling., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - The Day of the Locust., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - The Falcon and the Snowman., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 68)
    - Far from the Madding Crowd., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - Honky Tonk Freeway., press kit, clippings (Box 68)
    - Madame Sousatzka., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - Marathon Man., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
    - Midnight Cowboy., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 68)
  - Schlesinger, John (cont.) (Box 69)
    - Pacific Heights., press kit, clippings (Box 69)
    - Sunday Bloody Sunday., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 69)
    - Yanks., notes, clippings (Box 69)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Schlesinger (Box 69)
  - Schlöndorff, Volker (Box 69)
    - Un amour de Swann (Swann in Love)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 69)
    - Der Fangschuß (Coup de grâce)., notes, program, clippings (Box 69)
    - Der Junge Törless (Young Torless)., notes, program, clippings (Box 69)
    - Strohfeuer (A Free Woman)., notes, clippings (Box 69)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 69)
  - Schlossberg, Julian, Daniel Goldberg and Anthony Potenza (Box 69)
    - No Nukes., press kit, clippings (Box 69)
  - Schoendorffer, Pierre (Box 69)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 69)
  - Schnell, Maximilian (Box 69)
    - Erste Liebe (First Love - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 69)
    - Der Fußgänger (The Pedestrian - U.S.)., notes, clippings (Box 69)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Schnell (Box 69)
  - Schrader, Paul (Box 69)
    - Affliction., script (Box 69)
    - American Gigolo., notes, press release, clippings (Box 69)
    - Blue Collar., (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - Cat People., press kit, clippings (Box 69)
    - The Comfort of Strangers., press release, clippings (Box 69)
    - Hardcore., (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - Light of Day., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 69)
    - Light Sleeper., clippings (Box 69)
    - Mishima: A Life in Four Chapters., (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - Patty Hearst., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 69)
    - Clippings concerning Schrader (Box 69)
  - Schroeder, Barbet (Box 69)
    - Single White Female., list of credits, photographs (Box 69)
  - Schultz, Carl (Box 69)
    - Careful, He Might Hear You., notes, publicity, press kit, photographs, clippings (Box 69)
  - Schumacher, Joel (Box 69)
    - Cousins., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 69)
    - D.C. Cab., (2 folders) (Box 69)
    - Flatliners., publicity, press kit, photographs, clippings (Box 69)
    - The Incredible Shrinking Woman., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 69)
    - The Lost Boys., press release, press kit, color slides, clippings (Box 69)
    - St. Elmo's Fire., notes, clippings (Box 69)
  - Scola, Ettore (Box 69)
    - Le Bal., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 69)
    - C'eravamo tanto amati (We All Loved Each Other So Much)., notes, clippings (Box 69)
    - Dramma della gelosia - tutti i particolari in cronaca (The Pizza Triangle)., publicity, clippings (Box 69)
    - Una Giornata particolare (A Special Day)., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 69)
    - La Nuit de Varennes., publicity, clippings (Box 69)
    - Passione d'amore., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 69)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 69)
  - Scorsese, Martin (Box 70)
    - After Hours., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 70)
    - Alice Doesn't Live Here Anymore., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 70)
    - American Boy: A Profile of: Steven Prince., notes, clippings (Box 70)
    - Cape Fear., notes, clippings (Box 70)
    - The Color of Money., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 70)
    - Goodfellas., clippings (Box 70)
    - The King of Comedy., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 70)
    - Kundun., press kit (Box 70)
    - The Last Temptation of Christ., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 70)
    - The Last Waltz., notes, clippings (Box 70)
    - Mean Streets., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 70)
    - New York, New York., (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Raging Bull., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 70)
    - Taxi Driver., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 70)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 70)
    - Materials concerning Scorsese (Box 70)
  - Scott, George C. (Box 70)
    - The Savage Is Loose., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 70)
    - Materials concerning other films and Scott (Box 70)
  - Scott, Ridley (Box 70)
    - Alien., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 70)
    - Black Rain., (2 folders) (Box 70)
    - Blade Runner., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 70)
    - The Duellists., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 70)
    - Legend., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 70)
    - Someone To Watch Over Me., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 70)
  - Scott, Tony (Box 70)
    - Beverly Hills Cop II., notes, clippings (Box 70)
    - Days of Thunder., clippings (Box 70)
    - The Hunger., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 70)
    - Revenge., press kit, clippings (Box 70)
    - Top Gun., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 70)
  - Scribner, George (Box 70)
    - Oliver & Company., press kit, clippings (Box 70)
  - Seidelman, Susan (Box 70)
    - Desperately Seeking Susan., (2 folders) (Box 70)
  - Seidelman, Susan (cont.) (Box 71)
    - Making Mr. Right., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 71)
    - Smithereens., (2 folders) (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 71)
  - Seiter, William A. (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 71)
  - Sellers, Peter (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning other films and Sellers, (2 folders) (Box 71)
  - Sembene, Ousmane (Box 71)
    - Emitai., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning other films and Sembene (Box 71)
  - Shanley, John Patrick (Box 71)
    - Joe Versus the Volcano., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 71)
    - Clippings concerning Shanley (Box 71)
  - Shapiro, Ken (Box 71)
    - The Groove Tube., notes, clippings (Box 71)
    - Modern Problems., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 71)
  - Sharpsteen, Ben (Box 71)
    - Water Birds., photographs (Box 71)
  - Shear, Barry (Box 71)
    - Wild in the Streets., publicity, clippings (Box 71)
  - Shebib, Donald (Box 71)
    - Goin' Down the Road., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - Heartaches., (2 folders) (Box 71)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 71)
  - Shelton, Ron (Box 71)
    - Bull Durham., notes, press release, press kit (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 71)
  - Shepard, Sam (Box 71)
    - Far North., clippings (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning Shepard (Box 71)
  - Sheridan, Jim (Box 71)
    - The Field., notes, script, clippings (Box 71)
    - In the Name of the Father., publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - My Left Foot., notes, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 71)
  - Shinoda, Masahiro (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning various films and Shinoda (Box 71)
  - Shyer, Charles (Box 71)
    - Baby Boom., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 71)
    - Irreconcilable Differences., (2 folders) (Box 71)
  - Siegel, Don (Box 71)
    - The Beguiled., publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - Charley Varrick., publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - Dirty Harry., press release, photographs, clippings (Box 71)
    - Escape from Alcatraz., publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - Jinxed!, notes, publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - Madigan., notes (Box 71)
    - The Shootist., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning other films and Siegel (Box 71)
  - Silleck, Bayley and Francis Thompson (Box 71)
    - On the Wing., press kit, color slides (Box 71)
  - Silver, Joan Micklin (Box 71)
    - Between the Lines., notes (Box 71)
  - Simon, Frank (Box 71)
    - The Queen., notes (Box 71)
  - Simoneau, Yves (Box 71)
    - Perfectly Normal., notes, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 71)
  - Siodmak, Robert (Box 71)
    - The Crimson Pirate., notes, photographs, clippings (Box 71)
    - The Killers., (see also: Box 116) (Box 71)
    - The Spiral Staircase., photographs, clippings (Box 71)
    - The Suspect., (for clippings see: Box 116) (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning other films, (see also: Box 116) (Box 71)
  - Sirk, Douglas (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 71)
  - Sjöberg, Alf (Box 71)
    - Fröken Julie (Miss Julie - U.S.)., notes, publicity, printed item, clippings (Box 71)
    - Hets (Torment - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 71)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Sjöberg (Box 71)
  - Sjöman, Vilgot (Box 71)
    - Jag är nyfiken - en film i gult (I Am Curious (Yellow) - U.S.)., notes, press release, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 71)
    - Syskonbädd 1782 (My Sister My Love - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 71)
  - Sjöström, Victor (Box 71)
    - Printed items and Clippings concerning Sjöström (Box 71)
  - Skolimowski, Jerzy (Box 71)
    - Deep End., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 71)
    - The Lightship., press kit, clippings (Box 71)
    - Moonlighting., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 71)
    - Walkower (Walkover - U.S.)., notes, publicity, photographs (Box 71)
    - Clippings concerning other films and Skolimowski (Box 71)
  - Smart, Ralphotographs (Box 71)
    - Curtain Up., program, photographs (Box 71)
  - Smight, Jack (Box 71)
    - Airport 1975., (see also: Box 116) (Box 71)
    - Loving Couples., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 71)
    - No Way to Treat a Lady., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 71)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 71)
  - Smith, Peter (Box 71)
    - No Surrender., press kit, clippings (Box 71)
  - Soderbergh, Steven (Box 72)
    - Sex, Lies, and Videotape., (2 folders) (Box 72)
  - Solanas, Fernando E. (Box 72)
    - La Hora de los hornos: Notas y testimonios sobre el neocolonialismo, la violencia y la liberación (The Hour of the Furnaces - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 72)
  - Solas, Humberto (Box 72)
    - Un Hombre de éxito (A Successful Man - U.S.)., ms (Box 72)
    - Lucía., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 72)
  - Sonnenfeld, Barry (Box 72)
    - The Addams Family., photographs (Box 72)
  - Sontag, Susan (Box 72)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 72)
  - Spears, Ross (Box 72)
    - Agee., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 72)
    - The Electric Valley., press kit (Box 72)
  - Spheeris, Penelope (Box 72)
    - The Decline of Western Civilization., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 72)
    - The Decline of Western Civilization Part II: The Metal Years., publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 72)
    - The Boys Next Door., notes, clippings (Box 72)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 72)
  - Spielberg, Steven (Box 72)
    - 1941., notes, clippings (Box 72)
    - Always., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 72)
    - Amazing Stories - The Mission (television)., notes, clippings (Box 72)
    - Close Encounters of the Third Kind., (2 folders) (see also: Box 116) (Box 72)
    - The Color Purple., (2 folders) (Box 72)
    - Duel., clippings (Box 72)
    - E.T. the Extra-Terrestrial., (3 folders) (Box 72)
    - Indiana Jones and the Last Crusade., (3 folders) (Box 72)
    - Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 72)
    - Jaws., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 72)
    - Raiders of the Lost Ark., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 72)
    - The Sugarland Express., emph: Dialogue on Film (Box 72)
    - Twilight Zone: The Movie (Segment 2)., press kit, clippings (Box 72)
    - Materials concerning other films and Spielberg (Box 72)
    - Newsweek interview (copy) (Box 72)
  - Spottiswoode, Roger (Box 72)
    - Air America., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 72)
    - The Best of Times., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 72)
    - The Pursuit of D.B. Cooper., press kit, clippings (Box 72)
    - Shoot to Kill., notes, publicity, photographs, clippings (Box 72)
    - Terror Train., photographs, clippings (Box 72)
    - Turner & Hooch., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 72)
    - Under Fire., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 72)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 72)
  - Stallone, Sylvester (Box 73)
    - Paradise Alley., (for publicity see: Box 116) (Box 73)
    - Rocky II., clippings (Box 73)
    - Rocky III., publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Rocky IV., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Staying Alive., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Clippings concerning Stallone (Box 73)
  - Starrett, Jack (Box 73)
    - Cleopatra Jones., notes, clippings (Box 73)
  - Steinberg, David (Box 73)
    - Going Berserk., press kit (Box 73)
  - Stern, Bert (Box 73)
    - Jazz on a Summer's Day., notes, clippings (Box 73)
  - Stern, Steven Hilliard (Box 73)
    - Draw!, publicity, photographs (Box 73)
  - Sternberg, Josef von (Box 73)
    - Das Blaue Engel (The Blue Angel - U.S.)., notes, printed item, program, photographs, clippings (Box 73)
    - Blonde Venus., pressbook (Box 73)
    - An Index to the Films of Josef von Sternberg (reprint from Sight and Sound no. 17); The Cinema of Josef von Sternberg (brochure) (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous Materials concerning von Sternberg, (see also: Box 116) (Box 73)
  - Stevens, George (Box 73)
    - A Place in the Sun., (see also: Box 116) (Box 73)
    - Shane., printed item, photographs, clippings (Box 73)
    - The Talk of the Town., photographs, clippings (Box 73)
    - Materials concerning other films, (see also: Box 116) (Box 73)
  - Stevenson, Robert (Box 73)
    - Back Street., photographs (Box 73)
    - Bedknobs and Broomsticks., notes, clippings (Box 73)
  - Stone, Oliver (Box 73)
    - Born on the Fourth of July., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 73)
    - The Doors., (2 folders) (Box 73)
    - The Hand., press kit, clippings (Box 73)
    - Platoon., (2 folders) (Box 73)
    - Salvador., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Talk Radio., notes, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 73)
    - Wall Street., (see also: Box 116) (Box 73)
  - Streisand, Barbra (Box 73)
    - The Prince of Tides., (for publicity see: Box 116) (Box 73)
    - Yentl., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Clippings concerning Streisand (Box 73)
  - Strick, Joseph (Box 73)
    - The Balcony., notes, clippings (Box 73)
    - Interviews with My Lai Veterans., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Road Movie., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Tropic of Cancer., publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Ulysses., publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 73)
  - Stroheim, Erich von (Box 73)
    - Greed., printed items, programs, clippings (Box 73)
    - Miscellaneous items concerning other films (Box 73)
    - Clippings concerning von Stroheim (Box 73)
  - Stuart, Mel (Box 73)
    - I Love My Wife., notes, clippings (Box 73)
  - Sturges, John (Box 73)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 73)
  - Sturges, Preston (Box 73)
    - Les Carnets du Major Thompson (The French, They Are a Funny Race - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 73)
    - The French They are a Funny Race., (see: Box 124) (Box 73)
    - The Sin of Harold Diddlebock (aka Mad Wednesday - U.S. reissue)., (see also: Box 116) (Box 73)
    - Unfaithfully Yours., (see also: Box 116) (Box 73)
    - Materials concerning other films and Sturges, (2 folders) (see also: Box 116) (Box 73)
  - Sucksdorff, Arne (Box 73)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 73)
  - Suzuki, Hideo (Box 73)
    - Kiri no naka no shojo (A Girl in the Mist - U.S.)., (see also: Box 116) (Box 73)
  - Swaim, Bob (Box 73)
    - Half Moon Street., press release, press kit, clippings (Box 73)
    - Masquerade., notes, press kit, clippings (Box 73)
  - Syberberg, Hans-Jürgen (Box 73)
    - Hitler - ein Film aus Deutschland (Hitler: A Film from Germany - U.S.)., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 73)
  - Szabó, István (Box 73)
    - Àlmodozások kora (The Age of Daydreaming - U.S.)., notes, publicity (Box 73)
    - Apa (Father - U.S.)., publicity (Box 73)
    - Bizalom (Confidence - U.S.)., publicity, clippings (Box 73)
    - Budapesti mesék (Budapest Tales - U.S.)., notes, publicity, program, clippings (Box 73)
    - Hanussen., clippings (Box 73)
    - Mephisto., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 73)
  - Szabó, István (cont.) (Box 74)
    - Oberst Redl (Colonel Redl - U.S.)., (2 folders) (Box 74)
    - Szerelmesfilm (Love film - U.S.)., program, clippings (Box 74)
    - Tüzoltó utca 25 (25 Fireman's Street - U.S.)., clippings (Box 74)
  - Szalapski, James (Box 74)
    - Heartworn Highways., press kit (Box 74)
  - Szwarc, Jeannot (Box 74)
    - Jaws 2., press release, clippings (Box 74)
    - Santa Claus., press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 74)
    - Supergirl., (2 folders) (Box 74)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 74)
  - Tacchella, Jean Charles (Box 74)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 74)
  - Tahimik, Kidlat (Box 74)
    - Mababangong bangungot (Perfumed Nightmare - U.S.)., press release, clippings (Box 74)
  - Tanner, Alain (Box 74)
    - Une flame dans mon coeur (A Flame in My Heart)., notes, press release, clippings (Box 74)
    - Jonas qui aura 25 ans en l'an 2000 (Jonah Who Will Be 25 in the Year 2000)., publicity, clippings (Box 74)
    - La Salamandre (The Salamander)., publicity, clippings (Box 74)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 74)
    - Materials concerning Tanner (Box 74)
  - Tarkovsky, Andrei (Box 74)
    - Nostalghia., notes, press release, publicity, clippings (Box 74)
    - Solyaris (Solaris - U.S.)., (2 folders) (Box 74)
    - Materials concerning other films and Tarkovsky (Box 74)
  - Tati, Jacques (Box 74)
    - Jour de fête (The Big Day - U.S.)., program, photographs, clippings (Box 74)
    - Mon oncle (My Uncle - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 74)
    - Les Vacances de Monsieur Hulot (Mr. Hulot's Holiday - U.S.)., photographs, clippings (Box 74)
    - Clippings concerning other films (Box 74)
    - Clippings and printed items concerning Tati (Box 74)
  - Taurog, Norman (Box 74)
    - Materials concerning various films (Box 74)
  - Tavernier, Bertrand (Box 74)
    - Coup de torchon (Clean Slate)., notes, press release, press kit, clippings (Box 74)
    - 'Round Midnight., notes, press kit, photographs, clippings (Box 74)
    - Un semaine de vacances (A Week's Vacation)., publicity, clippings (Box 74)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 74)
  - Taviani, Paolo and Vittorio Taviani (Box 74)
    - Allonsanfan., press release, clippings (Box 74)
    - Good Morning, Babylon., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 74)
    - Kaos (Chaos - U.S.)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 74)
    - La Notte di San Lorenzo (Night of the Shooting Stars)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 74)
    - Padre padrone (My Father, My Master - U.S.)., notes, program, publicity, clippings (Box 74)
    - Materials concerning other films (Box 74)
  - Teague, Lewis (Box 74)
    - Alligator., notes, clippings (Box 74)
    - The Jewel of the Nile., press release, publicity, clippings (Box 74)
    - Navy Seals., press kit (Box 74)
  - Téchiné, André (Box 74)
    - Barocco., notes, press release, publicity, press kit, clippings (Box 74)
    - Le Lieu du crime (Scene of the Crime)., notes, program, clippings (Box 74)
    - Souvenirs d'en France (French Provincial)., notes, publicity, clippings (Box 74)